# **HENRY CHEN**

Ln. 435, Sec. 3, Heping E. Rd., Xinyi Dist., Taipei City M: +886952890993 holyman1010@gmail.com https://goo.gl/A6k0PL

#### **Profile**

User-centered product designer with over 10 years of experience in structuring, developing and implementing digital design strategies. Innovative use of technology and CRO to drive user experience and achieve business goal. Be good at coordinate cross-function to complete projects efficiently and satisfy customers with intuitive, user-friendly designs.

# **Areas of Expertise**

- Conversion rate optimization
- Strong collaborative skills
- User interface design skills
- Front-end programming skills
- Project management
- User research and interview skills
- Digital marketing analytics and optimization
- Excellent problem-solving skills

## **Work Experience**

**Product Design Lead** (4 direct reports)

AsiaYo.com - Taipei City, Taiwan

Apr 2017 - Present

- Develops, implements, and leading the company's design strategy.
- Transform high-level business strategies into a practical action plan.
- Utilizing monitor tools to conduct CRO and user experience optimization.

#### Sr.UI/UX Designer

May 2016 - April 2017

HongKu info Co.,Ltd - Taipei City, Taiwan

- Prioritizing project deliverables and assigning, reviewing, and approving work.
- Creating low/high fidelity prototypes and conducting user testing.
- Effectively develop UI in a clean, well structured, easily maintainable format.

#### **User Experience Design Specialist**

May 2016 - April 2017

SAP - Taipei City, Taiwan

- Served as UX consultant and created high-level wireframe, mockups and prototyping to communicate with related stakeholders.
- Guide and influence User-Centered Design Thinking methods and working process into diversity departments.
- Experienced in diverse projects(insurance, medical) and overcome technical issues.

### **Education**

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng), Department of Merchant Marine National Taiwan Ocean University - Keelung City, Taiwan

## **Technical skills**

Research, Information Architecture, Wireframing, Mockups, Prototyping, Team Management, Conversion Optimization, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript